<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Himalayan Borderlands</title>
    <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Himalayan Borderlands</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://khangchendzonga.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nepali Language Workshop</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/nepali/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/nepali/</guid>
      <description>In development: Nepali Language Workshop at University of Toronto with Laxmi Nath Shrestha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGBV Workshop</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/kgbv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/kgbv/</guid>
      <description>February 2019 In development: an intensive two-week workshop at the Kasturba Gandhi Balika Vidyalay School for Girls in Labang, West Sikkim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops with Ruth Gamble</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/gamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/gamble/</guid>
      <description>December 4: Outdoor Walk - “River Histories, Cultures, and Environments: Walking the Humber River”
Join U of T faculty, students, community members, and our guest Ruth Gamble, for a walking tour of the Humber River led by Alan Colley of Toronto Aboriginal Eco Tours.
December 5: Lecture and discussion on “Concreting the World&amp;rsquo;s Highest River: Environmental, Cultural and Geopolitical Impacts of Developing the Yarlung Tsangpo (Brahmaputra) River”
The transboundary Yarlung Tsangpo (Brahmaputra) River flows across the Tibetan Plateau at an average altitude of more than 4000 meters, before entering northeast India through the world&amp;rsquo;s deepest gorge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/events/</guid>
      <description>April 2019 In development: Nepali Language Workshop at University of Toronto with Laxmi Nath Shrestha from Kathmandu. Laxmi Nath Shrestha is a widely acclaimed Nepali language teacher who has served as a teacher of several generations of Nepal Studies scholars. Over the last 15 years he has been conducting courses at universities in Heidelberg, Lisbon, Marburg, and Vienna. In April 2019 he will be teaching in Toronto.
February 2019 In development: an intensive two-week workshop at the Kasturba Gandhi Balika Vidyalay School for Girls in Labang, West Sikkim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/gallery/</guid>
      <description>   I m g 0234
      I m g 0380
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/team/</guid>
      <description>Damien Boltauzer Damien is an undergraduate in Anthropology at the Department for the Study of Religion at the University of Toronto. He has a deep interest in religious/sacred spaces and geographies in the Himalayan Buddhist world. He has conducted research with the KCC in Sikkim and also in Ladakh, and he is now studying for a year in Kathmandu.
Anna Balikci Denjongpa Anna has a Ph.D. in Anthropology from the School of Oriental and African Studies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>