<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Himalayan Borderlands</title>
    <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Himalayan Borderlands</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://khangchendzonga.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Project</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>With funding from the Canadian SSHRC Insight grant program, a five-year project entitled &amp;ldquo;Expeditions to Paradise: Sacred Travel in the Himalaya&amp;rdquo; is exploring how the world&amp;rsquo;s highest mountains are constructed as &amp;lsquo;sacred.&amp;rsquo;
Our goal is to map religious expression in written and oral depictions of Himalayan travel. In particular, we hope to shed light on how historical and contemporary travelogues, guidebooks and guiding discourses construct mountains as sacred, utopian, or otherwise religiously empowered; to reveal how individual transnational encounters define mountains in religious or spiritual terms, as expressed in oral histories of pilgrims, mountaineers, and residents of the Himalayan foothills; and to develop a history of Himalayan travel depicted as pilgrimage by local and international communities, contributing a globally informed perspective on sacred space and travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events at U of T</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/events/</guid>
      <description>Beyul Demojong: Bhutia Kingship and the Dawn of Buddhism and Identity among the Lhopos of Sikkim Kikee D. Bhutia, PhD Candidate at the University of Tartu and Visiting Doctoral Student at the University of Toronto
Bissel Room 417, 140 St George St, University of Toronto
Tuesday Febuary 27, 2018, 10:30 am
Join us for a presentation by visiting graduate student, Kikee D. Bhutia, with an overview of her doctoral research:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>