<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Himalayan Borderlands</title>
    <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Himalayan Borderlands</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://khangchendzonga.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nepali Language Workshop</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/nepali/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/nepali/</guid>
      <description>In development: Nepali Language Workshop at University of Toronto with Laxmi Nath Shrestha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGBV Workshop</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/kgbv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/kgbv/</guid>
      <description>February 2019 In development: an intensive two-week workshop at the Kasturba Gandhi Balika Vidyalay School for Girls in Labang, West Sikkim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops with Ruth Gamble</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/gamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/gamble/</guid>
      <description>December 4: Outdoor Walk - “River Histories, Cultures, and Environments: Walking the Humber River”
Join U of T faculty, students, community members, and our guest Ruth Gamble, for a walking tour of the Humber River led by Alan Colley of Toronto Aboriginal Eco Tours.
December 5: Lecture and discussion on “Concreting the World&amp;rsquo;s Highest River: Environmental, Cultural and Geopolitical Impacts of Developing the Yarlung Tsangpo (Brahmaputra) River”
The transboundary Yarlung Tsangpo (Brahmaputra) River flows across the Tibetan Plateau at an average altitude of more than 4000 meters, before entering northeast India through the world&amp;rsquo;s deepest gorge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Events</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/past/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/events/past/</guid>
      <description>February 27, 2018 Kikee D. Bhutia on &amp;ldquo;Beyul Demojong: Bhutia Kingship and the Dawn of Buddhism and Identity among the Lhopos of Sikkim&amp;rdquo;
Kikee&amp;rsquo;s paper aimed to situate the sacred landscape of Sikkim according to belief narratives that revolve around the arrival of Guru Padmasambhava. It is believed that when Guru Padmasambhava was on his way to Tibet, he passed the Hidden Land of Demojong and sanctified the land, taming supernatural beings by turning them into the guardian deities of the land and hiding terma in different parts of the land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/gallery/</guid>
      <description>   I m g 0234
      I m g 0380
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Histories</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/projects/histories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/projects/histories/</guid>
      <description>Text-historical research In Toronto, Frances Garrett, Khenpo Kunga Sherab, and Dakpa Gyatso have been studying Tibetan language guidebooks to hidden lands (sbas yul). An international workshop on &amp;ldquo;Hidden Lands in Himalayan Myth and History: Transformations of Beyul (sBas yul) through Time&amp;rdquo; was held in Toronto in December 2017, featuring thirteen paper presentations; this research is now being prepared as an edited volume.
In Sikkim, Anna Balikci-Denjongpa is working with monks from Pemayangtse monastery on a book that documents sacred sites in the Khangchendzonga National Park and the environs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Training and Community Engagement</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/projects/communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/projects/communities/</guid>
      <description>This project is designed around student and citizen engagement, drawing on models of public history and community-based research. From 2016-2018, Garrett and Price taught an immersive field course in Sikkim that focused on Buddhist pilgrimage travel, the influence of rivers on Himalayan cultures, and the interplay between religious institutions and environmental sustainability movements in the region.
In the summer of 2017, undergraduate Study of Religion student Damien Boltauzer worked with the KCC in Yuksam on digitizing their archival materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/team/</guid>
      <description>Damien Boltauzer Damien is an undergraduate in Anthropology at the Department for the Study of Religion at the University of Toronto. He has a deep interest in religious/sacred spaces and geographies in the Himalayan Buddhist world. He has conducted research with the KCC in Sikkim and also in Ladakh, and he is now studying for a year in Kathmandu.
Anna Balikci Denjongpa Anna has a Ph.D. in Anthropology from the School of Oriental and African Studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text-historical research</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/projects/texts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/projects/texts/</guid>
      <description>In Toronto, Frances Garrett, Khenpo Kunga Sherab, and Dakpa Gyatso have been studying Tibetan language guidebooks to hidden lands (sbas yul). An international workshop on &amp;ldquo;Hidden Lands in Himalayan Myth and History: Transformations of Beyul (sBas yul) through Time&amp;rdquo; was held in Toronto in December 2017, featuring thirteen paper presentations; this research is now being prepared as an edited volume.
In Sikkim, Anna Balikci-Denjongpa is working with monks from Pemayangtse monastery on documenting sacred sites in the Khangchendzonga National Park and the environs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>