<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Himalayan Borderlands</title>
    <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Himalayan Borderlands</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Project</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>With funding from the Canadian SSHRC Insight grant program, a five-year project entitled &amp;ldquo;Expeditions to Paradise: Sacred Travel in the Himalaya&amp;rdquo; is exploring how the world&amp;rsquo;s highest mountains are constructed as &amp;lsquo;sacred.&amp;rsquo;
Our goal is to map religious expression in written and oral depictions of Himalayan travel. In particular, we hope to shed light on how historical and contemporary travelogues, guidebooks and guiding discourses construct mountains as sacred, utopian, or otherwise religiously empowered; to reveal how individual transnational encounters define mountains in religious or spiritual terms, as expressed in oral histories of pilgrims, mountaineers, and residents of the Himalayan foothills; and to develop a history of Himalayan travel depicted as pilgrimage by local and international communities, contributing a globally informed perspective on sacred space and travel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events at U of T</title>
      <link>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://khangchendzonga.github.io/page/events/</guid>
      <description>February 27, 2018: Kikee D. Bhutia on &amp;ldquo;Beyul Demojong: Bhutia Kingship and the Dawn of Buddhism and Identity among the Lhopos of Sikkim&amp;rdquo; Kikee&amp;rsquo;s paper aimed to situate the sacred landscape of Sikkim according to belief narratives that revolve around the arrival of Guru Padmasambhava. It is believed that when Guru Padmasambhava was on his way to Tibet, he passed the Hidden Land of Demojong and sanctified the land, taming supernatural beings by turning them into the guardian deities of the land and hiding terma in different parts of the land.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>